ten.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Statement for LFP Internet Group, LLC

**Last Updated: April 19, 2017**

LFP Internet Group, LLC (“LFP”) and its affiliate companies (collectively, “we”, “us” or “our”), is an adult-oriented entertainment company that, among other things, publishes the globally-famous Hustler Magazine, produces adult films and operates retail sales outlets and casinos. We also operate several internet websites, web pages and sub-domains that link to this Privacy Policy, including without limitation, this website at www.hustler.com (collectively, the “Website”). In the operation of the Website, we and our third party service providers and partners sometimes gather certain information from and about visitors to and users of the Website (collectively, “you”). This Privacy Policy describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information we might collect from you when you visit or use the Website. It also describes your options regarding what types of information is collected from you, how it is used, and what we do to protect your information. 

Information collected by any service provider, strategic partner, third-party website or advertiser that processes a transaction, information, links to or is accessible from the Website is not covered by this Privacy Policy. Such information is covered by the privacy policies of such third parties, if any. Our use of such information is covered by this Privacy Policy. Any third parties that receive information via transactions or service offered through the Website, such as, for example, a payment processer, receive such information solely for the purpose of your transaction with us.

The Website is operated from the United States in accordance with laws of the United States, and with respect to residents of the State of California, USA, also complies with California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (as detailed below). If you are located outside of the United States, use of the Website is at your own risk and you are responsible for complying with your local and national laws. By using the Website and/or by providing us with any personal information, you acknowledge that (a) U.S. law provides a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of some other countries; (b) we will deal with your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and U.S. law; and (c) you hereby waive any claims that may arise under the laws and regulations that apply to you in any other country or jurisdiction.

This Privacy Policy, along with the [Terms of Use](https://hustler.com/terms/) also posted on our Website, set out the rules and policies governing use of the Website. We may change or update the Terms of Use and/or this Privacy Policy from time to time, so we urge you to check this page frequently. The date of the most recent update is shown at the top of this page. Revisions take effect upon posting. Your use of the Website following any such update and posting constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as amended and then in effect.

WHEN YOU ACCESS THE WEBSITE, YOU THEREBY AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY – PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS, CONTINUE TO ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

HOW AND WHAT INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED

Information may, now or later, be collected through a variety of means, including, without limitation, (i) automatically as you navigate through and interact with the Website, including via cookies, pixels, beacons, and other tracking technologies; (ii) via third parties, such as by certain of our service providers, and (iii) directly from you when you provide it to us, such as when you fill out forms on the Website, sign-up for a newsletter, make a purchase or your other activities on the Website.

**Types of information that may be collected from and about you, include:**  
Personal information – information that can be used to identify you personally including, without limitation, your name, signature, address, telephone number, e-mail address, screen name, credit card details, bank account or other payment information, and other information by which you may be personally identified either standing alone or which may become personally identifying when combined with other information. 

**Non-personal information**  
– information that does not identify Website users individually and that is not linked to any personal information including, without limitation, information regarding a Website user’s computer/device, Internet connection, IP address, browser types, operating systems or platforms, general geographic location, and the name and location of Internet Service Providers, information regarding the use of our Website (including referring pages and the exiting websites, clickstream data, the search terms you enter on the Website, browsing/navigation/visit history and details, and traffic patterns relating to the Website. Non-personal information may include personally identifiable information that has been de-identified/rendered anonymous. 

**Information You Provide:** It is your choice whether to provide any non-automatically collected information to us; however, in some cases personal information will be required in order for you to make purchases, become a registered user or subscriber, gain access to certain features, services or content on the Website, to participate in certain Website activities or for us to provide certain services to you.

**Automatically-Collected Information:** Automatically-collected information is mostly statistical data that does not contain personal information. However, if automatically-collected information does contain personal information, such information will be treated as personal information under this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:**

The Website may place “cookies”, a small file that may be stored on your device if your web browser or device settings permit, to collect certain information from you. Cookies allow us to customize your experience and respond to you as an individual in your use of the Website by recognizing you when you return, remembering your viewing preferences, username and passwords, etc. The Website may also use Flash Cookies or local stored objects in connection with your Website preferences and navigation. 

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. Some cookies are deleted when you close your browser, others remain even after you close your browsing session. If you prefer, you can set your web browser to refuse cookies, except Flash cookies. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies – you must set this preference separately. You may also delete a cookie manually from your hard drive through your internet browser or other programs. You may not be able to enjoy the full functionality of the Website if cookies are disabled.

The Website may currently or in future also utilize technology similar to cookies, such as pixel tags, web beacons and clear gifs, to enable us to optimize the content and usability of the Website, how the Website interacts with you, and to enable us to collect other information about you and your visit to the Website.

The information gathered by us and our service providers through cookies and similar technologies may be matched or combined with data provided by you or another party. To the extent that our service providers are using such technologies, we do not control such use of technologies or the resulting information, and are not responsible for the policies of such companies.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We and our service providers may use your personal information for the purposes disclosed to you or as otherwise permitted or required by law, including or which may include: to provide, track, and process the services, purchases and transactions that you request; to process memberships, newsletter subscriptions, enrollments and applications; to accommodate your preferences, to personalize and enhance your experience on the Website; to monitor, track, and analyze Website usage and trends, to personalize and improve the Website’s functionality; to validate your identity, verify communications received from you, to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests for information and complaints; to send you notices about purchases, subscriptions, and changes to our terms, conditions and policies; to conduct customer satisfaction, market research or quality assurance surveys; to assist us in developing new goods or services; to conduct and administer sweepstakes, prize drawings and other contests; for marketing purposes including interest-based advertising, other targeted promotions, to send promotional materials, and notices about special promotions, offers, events or opportunities; to send marketing communications about products and services offered by our partners and other third parties; to send confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate use of and administration and operation of the Website; to protect the security or integrity of the Website and of our business; to prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities; to investigate and resolve disputes and problems, and to otherwise comply with applicable laws and regulations; to enforce our Website Terms of Use and contractual obligations; to identify you and to share your information as described herein; for any other purpose that is disclosed to you at the point of collection of such information, for any purpose for which you provide your prior consent and for any other lawful purpose.

**SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share non-personal information with any third parties for any lawful purpose. Unless otherwise prohibited by law, we may also disclose personal information collected from or about you to the following types of third parties and for the following purposes:

  * **Service Providers:** We may share your information with our service providers and business partners in connection with services such as hosting, payment processing and billing, delivering packages and fulfillment, data storage, security, customer service, extended warranty services, credit reporting, customer relationship management, accounting, auditing, administering sweepstakes, surveys, email and mailing services, marketing or other relationships for joint marketing purposes or such partners’ own marketing purposes in connection with the operation of the Website or our business.
  * **Affiliated Companies & Corporate Transactions:** We may share your information with our parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies, successors and/or assigns, who may use personal information for any purpose disclosed in or consistent with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, in the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, bankruptcy, reorganization, or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties any and/or all information collected from or about you. 
  * **Legal:** We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify you and, where permitted or required by law, we may provide information about or relating to you, including any personally identifiable information about you, to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order, subpoena, government request for information, or other legal or regulatory requirements; (b) protect or defend our rights or property, our Website, or other Website users; (c) respond to claims that any posting or other content of our Website violates the rights or property of any third party, including without limitation providing information necessary to satisfy the Digital Millennium Copyright Act; (d) to protect the health and safety of our Website’s users or the general public; (d) to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use; or (f) to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it to us, and otherwise with your consent.

**HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS**

Some web browsers offer a “do not track” setting indicating your preferences regarding tracking, which is separate and distinct from declining cookies in your browser settings. The Website does not recognize web browser “do not track” signals at this time. We may work with third parties that use tracking technologies on the Website to facilitate the provision of personalized advertising materials to you. Such technologies may collect information about your activities on the Website over time and across third-party websites and services, your interaction with our advertising and communications, and use this information to determine which advertisements you see on third-party websites and applications.

**HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS**

Information about your activities on the Website may, now or later, be collected by third parties through unique identifiers, cookies, pixels, beacons and other technologies. Such information may be used to make predictions about metrics applicable to your preferences and receptiveness to various advertising. We use Google’s Remarketing service with Google AdWords to show you our ads as you browse other websites around the Internet. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies and/or customize Google display network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager at <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. You can opt-out of Remarketing by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. If you want to permanently opt out of the DoubleClick cookie, you can install the DoubleClick opt out extension by clicking [here](https://myaccount.google.com/not-supported?ref=/settings/ads/plugin). From time to time we may use other advertising networks or service providers to show you our ads on other websites. Many advertising networks are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt-out of ad targeting from member companies, which you can access and review your options for opting out at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. However, even if you opt out of receiving tailored ads, you will continue to see ads but those ads may be less relevant to your interests.

**ANALYTICS**

In order to better understand and optimize our Website and your use of it, for business and market research purposes, for measuring conversion tracking, and measuring the effectiveness of our content and online advertising campaigns, we work with service providers to provide analytics data via cookies alone or in conjunction with unique identifiers, pixels, beacons and other tracking technologies which collect information about you when you use the Website.

For example, through our provider, Google Analytics, data is collect about use of the Website. We do not provide Google Analytics with your name, phone number, email address or credit card information and instead assign a random number to your usage so that Google Analytics can identify each unique user of our Website. If you prefer to limit or eliminate the data that Google Analytics collects about your use of our Website, use Google Analytics "Opt-out" option at: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

To the extent that chat rooms, blogs, message boards, bulletin boards, or similar public forums are provided on the Website for you and other users to communicate with us or with each other, the provisions of this Privacy Policy do not apply to information, including personal information, that you post to any such public forums (unless specifically required by law or regulation). We urge you to take special care before posting any information in a public forum because it may be seen or collected by anyone, therefore, we are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Website.

**CHILDREN/SEXUALLY EXPLICIT MATERIAL**

ALL CONTENT AND MATERIALS, INCLUDING MESSAGES, AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS, CONTAINED ON THE WEBSITE ARE INTENDED FOR DISTRIBUTION EXCLUSIVELY TO CONSENTING ADULTS IN LOCATIONS WHERE ALL THE CONTENT, MATERIALS, MESSAGES AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS CONTAINED AT THE WEBSITE DO NOT VIOLATE ANY COMMUNITY STANDARDS OR ANY FEDERAL, STATE OR LOCAL LAW OR REGULATION OF THE UNITED STATES OR ANY LAW OF ANY OTHER COUNTRY. NO PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS (TWENTY-ONE (21) IN PLACES WHERE EIGHTEEN YEARS IS NOT THE AGE OF MAJORITY) MAY DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY VIEW OR POSSESS ANY OF THE CONTENT AND MATERIALS OF THE WEBSITE OR PLACE ANY ORDERS FOR ANY GOODS OR SERVICES ADVERTISED AT OR ON THE WEBSITE. ANY ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE OR ANY OF ITS CONTENT AND MATERIALS BY A MINOR SHALL CONSTITUTE UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO STORED COMMUNICATIONS PROHIBITED BY THE STORED COMMUNICATIONS ACT, 18 U.S.C. SECTIONS 2510-2520 AND VIOLATIONS OF OTHER LAWS.

YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE AND REPRESENT THAT YOU KNOW AND UNDERSTAND THAT THE CONTENT AND MATERIALS PRESENTED AT, AND/OR DOWNLOADABLE FROM, THE WEBSITE INCLUDE EXPLICIT VISUAL, AUDIO, AND/OR TEXTUAL DEPICTIONS OF NUDITY AND SEXUAL ACTIVITIES, WHICH MAY INCLUDE, WITHOUT LIMITATION, HETEROSEXUAL, BI-SEXUAL, HOMOSEXUAL, AND/OR TRANSSEXUAL ACTIVITIES OF AN EXPLICIT SEXUAL NATURE; THAT YOU ARE FAMILIAR WITH MATERIALS OF THIS KIND; THAT YOU ARE NOT OFFENDED BY SUCH MATERIALS; AND THAT BY AGREEING TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS YOU ARE WARRANTING TO THE COMPANY THAT YOU ARE INTENTIONALLY AND KNOWINGLY SEEKING ACCESS TO SUCH EXPLICIT SEXUAL MATERIALS FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL VIEWING FOR ENTERTAINMENT AND/OR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY.

YOU HEREBY AFFIRM AND WARRANT THAT YOU ARE CURRENTLY OVER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS (TWENTY ONE (21) IN PLACES WHERE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS IS NOT THE AGE OF MAJORITY) AND ARE CAPABLE OF LAWFULLY ENTERING INTO AND EXECUTING THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from individuals under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian of an individual under the age of 18 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us without your permission, please contact us at privacy@lfp.com or as provided in the “Contact Us” section below. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 may request deletion of such child’s personally identifiable information as well as prohibit its use. 

**SECURITY**

The security of your personal information is important to us and in order to prevent its unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you. However, no electronic storage, safeguards, security protocols nor means of transmitting data over the Internet can be nor is entirely safe and secure -- for example risks of computer viruses, malicious software and hacker attacks. Thus, while we strive to take reasonable steps to protect your personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant its security, and you agree that we are not responsible for its theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure. We also recommend that you do not include any non-public personal or sensitive personal information such as passwords, social security numbers, credit card details or bank account information in any emails that you send to us. We will not contact you by email or otherwise seeking such information.

**OTHER WEBSITES/LINKS**

Our Website may contain links to enable you to easily visit other websites of interest. However, once you use such links to leave our Website, you should note that we do not have any control over any other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide when visiting such websites and such websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and you should read the privacy policies of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for third party websites. 

**CONTROLLING YOUR INFORMATION**

You can contact us at any time, as described in the “Contact Us” section below, to update or correct certain personal information, to opt-out of receiving commercial (not transactional) emails, or otherwise inquire about your information. Also, if you have registered with or joined the Website, you can login to your account to change certain information and preferences. 

Please allow sufficient time for your preferences to be processed. Even if you opt out of receiving marketing messages, we may still contact you for transactional purposes like confirming or following up on an order or service request, asking you to review a product or service you have ordered, or notifying you of product recalls. If you later opt back into getting marketing communications from us, we will remove your information from our opt-out databases. 

We may, at times, provide you with the option to set your email preferences. You may also opt-out of receiving future commercial emails from us by following the “Unsubscribe” instructions contained in any commercial emails that you receive from us at any time and we will make the requested change in our active databases within a reasonable time. However, we may not be able to fulfill certain requests while allowing you access to certain benefits and features and you may continue to receive certain transactional, customer service, account and profile messages, and similar communications. Importantly, we may not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties to whom we already provided your personal information as of the date of your opt-out request. Additionally, discussed above, you can also set your web browser to refuse browser cookies (but not Flash cookies).

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Residents of the State of California may, under the “Shine the Light” law (California Civil Code Section 1798.83), request from certain businesses with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, a list of third parties to which the business, during the immediately preceding calendar year, has disclosed certain personally identifiable information for direct marketing purposes. We are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year. To make such a request you please contact us in accordance with the contact details provided below and with the subject heading “California Privacy Rights”, include an attestation to the fact that you are a California resident, and provide a current physical California address for our response.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to exercise the choices discussed above, please contact us (a) by email at privacy@lfp.com, or (b) by postal mail at Flynt Management Group, LLC, 8484 Wilshire Blvd. Suite 900, Beverly Hills, CA 90021, Attn: Legal Dept/Privacy.
